A Guide to the Papers of the League of Women Voters of Hampton Roads, 1956-1999
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Voters Service
  - Voting Information
    - Voting Information, 1991 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Facts About the League & Facts for Voters, 1992 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Calendars and Voter Sheets, 1996 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Voting Information, 1996-1997 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 12)
    - VS-Voter Publications (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Voter Guides
    - "Make Democracy Work: A Guide to Voter Guides for Local Leagues" (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Voter Guides, 1970 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Voter Guides, 1974-76 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Voter Guides, 1977 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Voter Guides, 1978 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Voter Guides, 1979 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Voter Guides, 1980 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Voter Guides, 1981 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Voter Guides, 1982 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Voter Guides, 1984 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Voter Guides, 1985 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Voter Guides, 1986 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Voter Guides, 1988 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Voter Guides, 1996 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Proposed Constitutional Amendments-"Victims Rights," 1996 (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Political Parties (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Voter Guides-Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Candidate Questionnaires
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1970 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1971 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1972 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1973 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1974 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1975 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1976 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1977 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1978 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1979 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1980 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1981 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1985 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1986 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1989 (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, 1990s (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Candidate Questionnaires, undated (Box-folder Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Political Accountablity and Voting Records
    - Political Accountablity and Voting Record I (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Political Accountablity and Voting Record II (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 2)
    - LWV Reports from the Hill (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Election Results and Reporting
    - Reporting on Elections, 1966, 1972, 1981 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Reporting on Elections, 1982, 1984, 1985, 1986 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Election Results, 1992 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Congressional/Legislative Interviews
    - Legislative Interivew Tips (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Congressional Interviews, 1965-1969 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Congressional Interviews, 1970-1972 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Congressional Interviews, 1975 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Congressional Interviews: 1977, 1979, 1980, 1982, 1987 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Legislative Interviews, 1985-1986 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Legislative Interviews, 1992 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Candidate Watchers, 1993 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Candidate Debates and Forums
    - "Face to Face: A Guide to Candidate Debates" (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Debate Format I (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Debate Format II (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 17)
    - LWV Sponsored Senatorial Debates, 1984 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Congressional Debates, 1986 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 19)
    - LWV Sponsored Congressional Debate, 1986 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 20)
    - LWV State Senatorial Debate, 1987 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Debates '88 2nd Congressional District, VA (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Presidential Debates, 1976, 1980, 1988 (Box-folder Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Presidential Debates, 1987 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Presidential Debates, 1988 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Beach City Council Candidate Forum, 1992 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Fredericksburg Candidates Forum, 1979 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 4)
  - WHRO Interviews
    - WHRO Interviews I (same order as orginal file) (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 5)
    - WHRO Interviews II (same order as orginal file) (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 6)
    - WHRO Interviews III (same order as orginal file) (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 7)
    - WHRO Transcripts I, 1985-1986 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 8)
    - WHRO Transcripts II, 1986 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 9)
    - WHRO Radio, General Assembely Reports (Tape) (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Articles and News Clippings
    - Voters Service Clippings, 1960s (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Voters Service Clippings, 1971-1975 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Voters Service Clippings, 1976-1979 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Voters Service Clippings, 1980s (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Voters Service Clippings, 1990s (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Voters Service Clippings, undated (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Voters Service Publications
    - VS Publications: Local Phase (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Voting Publications of Other Leagues (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Ideas from Other Leagues (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Voters Service Kit, 1972 (Box-folder Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Voters Service Miscellaneous
    - Voters Service, 1960s (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Voters Service, 1972-1974 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Voters Service, 1975-1976 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Voters Service, 1977-1978 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Voters Service, 1979-1980 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Voters Service, 1981 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Voters Services and Information, 1984-1986 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Voters Service, 1992 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Voters Service, 1995-1996 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Voters Service, [undated] (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 10)
    - "The League of Women Voters recommends that you make election '80 a real world lab," 1979 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 11)
- Issues and Studies
  - Summaries and Positions
    - Positioned for Action State Positions Pub. #AP135 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Categorical Assistance Report & Positions on Issues (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Positions-Local and State, 1971-1996 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Position Statements [LWV-VA], 1979 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Position Paper: LWV of VA, 1980 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 16)
    - General Issues [LWV-VA], 1992-1995 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 17)
    - LWV of Virginia Positions in Brief, 1996 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Positions & Issues: Election '96, 1996 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Impact on Issues-National Positions, 1990-1992 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Impact on Issues: A Leader's Guide to National Programs, 1990-1992 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 21)
    - LWV Impact on Issues, 1994-1996 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Study Guide: How to Conduct Studies (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Publication Production: How to Guidebook, 1974-1982 (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 24)
    - LWVUS Publications I (Box-folder Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Research, Studies, and Publications
    - Adult Domestic Violence Study I (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Adult Domestic Violence Study II (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 2)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science-Project I (same order as original folder) (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 3)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science-Project II (same order as original folder) (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 4)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science-Project III (same order as original folder) (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Financing (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 6)
    - "Child Day Care Report," February, 1984 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Child Care (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 8)
    - "Child Care: Investment in VA's Future" (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 9)
    - "State Plan for Child Day Care" (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Child Day Care Issues, 1985-1987 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Children at Risk (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 12)
    - City Planning, 1971 (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 13)
    - N.R. Clean Air (Box-folder Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Dillon Rule (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Early Voting I (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Early Voting II (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Electoral College and the Presidency (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Education Funding (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Education Funding-State Study I (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Education Funding-State Study II (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Education (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Employment (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Energy, 1976-1980 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 10)
    - LWV Energy 1-15, 24-25 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Environmental Information (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Environmental Issues I (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Environmental Issues II (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 14)
    - "The Equal Rights Amendment," June, 1981 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 1)
    - The Equal Rights Amendment I (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 2)
    - The Equal Rights Amendment II (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Family Building Act, 1990 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 4)
    - The Federalist Papers Reexamined-League of Women Voters Education Fund (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Finance Issues (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 6)
    - State Finances (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 7)
    - LWV-"Financing Federal Goverment" I (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 8)
    - LWV-"Financing Federal Goverment" II (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 9)
    - The Garbage Primer-LWV, 1993 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Great Dismal Swamp Study (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Environment/Dismal Swamp (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Photos: Dismal Swamp (1967-69), ERA Rally, Union Square-San Fransisco (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 13)
    - "The Great Dismal Swamp of Virginia and North Carolina"-The Living Wilderness, Autumn 1970 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Green America-"The Good Earth" (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Green Space Study I (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Green Space Study II (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Green Space Study III (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Green Space Study IV (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Green Space-Back Bay (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Gun Control (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 6)
    - "Regional Cooperation in the Reduction of Gun Violence," also Sheriff's & Meeting Agendas, May 1, 1997 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Hampton Roads Regional Cooperation (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Hazardous Waste (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Health Care (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Housing (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 11)
    - City of Norfolk: Report of the Affordable Housing Task Force, April 8, 1997 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Affordable Housing: Clippings & Correspondence (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 13)
    - HOV Impact Analysis, Norfolk-Virginia Beach Expressway Booklet, December 1987 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Human Resources, 1963-1966, 1972-1975, 1980-1981 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Human Resources (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Employment (Human Resources) (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Fighting Hunger in Your Community: A Guide for the Development of Community Action Projects, League of Women Voters Education Fund (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Intergovermental Relations (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 19)
    - International Relations Policy (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 1)
    - International Relations I (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 2)
    - International Relations II (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 3)
    - International Relations-China Study (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 4)
    - International Relations-National Security (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Agenda for Security: Final Report, 1988 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 6)
    - International Relations-Trade (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 7)
    - International Relations-United Nations (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 8)
    - LWV Jail Study I (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 9)
    - LWV Jail Study II (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Southeastern Virginia Regional Jail Study Addendum, January 1989 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 1)
    - A Regional Jail for Southeastern Virginia (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Juvenile Justice Study (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Land Use (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Land Use Initiatives for Tidewater VA: The Next Step in Protecting the Bay, November 1987 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Land Use: VA Beach Expressway (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 6)
    - MacArthur Center (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Mental Health, 1984-1985 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Mental Health, 1986-1987 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Mental Health, 1987-1989 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Motor Voter-National Voter Registration Act (NVRA) (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Natural Resources, 1971-1979 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Natural Resources, 1980-1982 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Natural Resources, 1983 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Natural Resources, 1984-1986 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Norfolk School Study, 1967 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Local Schools Study, 1967 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Schools Study (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 18)
    - The Nuclear Waste Primer-A Handbook for Citizens, LWV Education Fund (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Nuclear Waste Primer-LWV, 1993 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Pay Equity (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 3)
    - LWV: America's Growing Dilemma-Pesticides in Food & Water-A Citizen's Guide (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Poverty (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Pro-Choice Information, Webster V. Reproductive Health Service, Inc., June 22, 1989 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Reapportionment & Redistricting (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Reapportionment I (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Reapportionment II (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Pamphlets for Reapportionment/Redistricting in Various States (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Reapportionment/Redistricting in Virginia, 1964-1966 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Reapportionment/Redistricting in Virginia, 1970 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Reapportionment/Redistricting in Virginia, 1978-1985 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Current Focus-"Reapportionment: Issues for the Eighties," League of Women Voters Education Fund, "Constitutional Amendment by Convention: An Untried Alternative," "The Voter, The Law, and the Ballot," "The Expanded Electorate: Theory and Practice," 1971-1979 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Redistricting, 1994 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Recycling/Waste Managment (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Religious Freedom (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 17)
    - School Desegregation (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Social Policy I (Regional, National, & International), 1978-1982 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Social Policy II (Regional, National, & International), 1988-1990 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Local Transportation, 1971-1972 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Transportation: Light Rail I, 1986-1988 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Transportation: Light Rail II (Publications), 1986-1988 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Norfolk (Busing Clippings) (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 1)
    - LWV Massachusetts-Transportation, 1972-1973 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 2)
    - LWV Massachusetts-Transportation, 1974 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 3)
    - "Strategies for Coping: The Range of Options"-by Patricia Van Matne McLaughlin and Nigel H.M. Wilson, December 2-4, 1987 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Uranium (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Cities/Urban Crisis (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Urban Brief 1, 3, 4, 5-"Source on Cities," "National Urban Policy: The President's Proposals," "Circuit Breakers for the Tax Overload," "Learning from the Urban Experience Abroad" (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Court System (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Waste: Choices for Communities-Concern, Inc. (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Water Conservation (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Water (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Water Resources, 1964-1965 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Water Resources & Land Use, 1966-1979 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 13)
    - LWV "Environmental Update on Water," "Update on Water," "Update on Section 208," April 1975; January 1977; December 1976 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 14)
    - LWV Facts and Issues-"The Water You Drink," "Who Pays for a Clean Stream," "Water for the Nation's Capital" (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 15)
    - League of Women Voters-"So you'd like to do something about water pollution" pamphlets (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 16)
    - LWV The Letter of the Law-"The Clean Water Act of 1977," 1977 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 17)
    - "Protect Your Groundwater" (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Welfare Reform (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Wetlands, 1991-1992 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Environment/Wetlands-Articles, 1990-1991 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 21)
    - "Who Should elect the President"-League of Women Voters of the United States, May 1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Women's Issues (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Women's Rights (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Women's Rights I (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Women's Rights II (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Women & Work Education Fund (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 6)
    - "Status of Women in VA" (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 4)
- Know Your Goverment
  - Know Your City Guides (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 1)
  - City Guides: Chesapeake, Tidewater Area (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 2)
  - City Guides: Hampton (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 3)
  - City of Norfolk (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Guide to Norfolk City Goverment (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Norfolk Story/City Goverment (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Know Your City Guides: Virginia Beach (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Beach-Misc. (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Beach Tommorrow, 1986 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 9)
  - A Citizen's Guide to Montgomery Co.-Christiansburg & Blacksburg, 1976 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Goverment I (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Goverment II (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Representative Goverment (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Potpourri (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 14)
- Artifacts
  - "Campaign for Election" Board Game (2) (Box Box 33)
  - "Your Vote Counts" Poster (2) (Box Box 33)
  - "Vote! Democracy is NOT a Spectator Sport" Bumper Sticker (1) (Box Box 33)
  - "Vote America" advertisement on Winn Dixie Bag (Box Box 33)